A Guide to the Papers of William B. Spong, 1965-1974
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Legislative
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Dismal Swamp, S. 2441 & H.R. 10511 1972, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Forest Land Management (S. 350 & S. 1734) 1971-1972 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Golden Eagle Passport Program, S. 2315 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Indian Affairs 1967-1972 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Land and Water Conservation Funds Act (S. 1401) 1968 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Land Use Planning (S. 632) 1972 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Menhaden Research 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Minerals, Materials and Fuels 1966-1968 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - National Environmental Policy Act 1972 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Parks and Recreation 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Parks and Recreation - Appomattox Manor, Hopewell, Virginia 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Parks and Recreation - Potomac River Basin 1967-1970 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Parks and Recreation - Redwood National Forest 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Parks and Recreation - Yorktown Colonial National Historical Park 1967 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Public Lands 1967-1970 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Shenandoah National Park, S. 3541 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Strip Mining 1970-1972, 6 folders (Box 50)
  - Judiciary 1967-1972, 10 folders (Box 50)
  - Judiciary - Administrative Practice and Procedures 1967 (Box 50)
  - Judiciary - Alexandria Waterfront Bill 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Judiciary - Anti-Trust and Monopoly 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 50)
  - Judiciary - Anti-Trust and Monopoly - Auto Repairs 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Anti-Trust and Monopoly - "Conglomerates: Concentration, Collusion, Control" - A Study 1970 Feb 15 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Anti-Trust and Monopoly - Medical Costs 1970 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Anti-Trust and Monopoly - Newspaper Preservation Act 1969-1970 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Bayh Resolution - Direct Popular Election 1967 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Church Related Programs 1968 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Civil Rights 1967-1969, 14 folders (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Civil Rights - Black Panthers 1970 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Civil Rights - Interference (H.R. 2516) 1968 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Civil Rights - King Demonstration 1968 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - College Benefit System 1968-1971, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Congressional Redistricting 1967 (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Constitutional Amendments 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Constitutional Amendments - Electoral College 1967-1969, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Judiciary - Constitutional Amendments - Electoral College 1970-1972, 7 folders (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Constitutional Convention - One Man, One Vote 1967-1969 (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Constitutional Rights 1966-1971, 3 folders (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Constitutional Rights - Flag Burning 1967-1969 (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Constitutional Rights - Polygraph Test 1971-1972 (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Constitutional Rights- Voluntary Confessions 1967 (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Copyrights, Patents and Trademarks 1965-1972, 7 folders (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Copyrights, Patents and Trademarks - Brown Morton Proposal to the Copyright Patent Bill 1967 (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Cost of Medical Care 1968 (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Crime 1967-1972, 9 folders (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Criminal Laws and Procedures 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 52)
  - Judiciary - Criminal Laws and Procedures - Drugs 1970 (Box 53)
  - Judiciary - Criminal Laws and Procedures - Riots and Disorders 1967-1968, 12 folders (Box 53)
  - Judiciary - Criminal Laws and Procedures - Riots and Disorders (Form Letter Reply) 1967 (Box 53)
  - Judiciary - Criminal Laws and Procedures - Riots and Disorders - Riot Commission Report 1966 (Box 53)
  - Judiciary - Cyclamates 1972 (Box 53)
  - Judiciary - Douglas Impeachment 1970 (Box 53)
  - Judiciary - Equal Rights Amendment 1967-1972 Mar 15, 14 folders (Box 53)
  - Judiciary - Equal Rights Amendment 1972 Mar 16-Nov, 4 folders (Box 54)
  - Judiciary - Federal Charters and Holidays 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 54)
  - Judiciary - Federal Charters and Holidays - Junior Achievement, Inc. 1971 (Box 54)
  - Judiciary - Federal Charters and Holidays - Martin Luther King, Jr. 1969-1970 (Box 54)
  - Judiciary - Federal Charters and Holidays - Monday Holiday 1967-1968 (Box 54)
  - Judiciary - Flora vs U.S. 1968 (Box 54)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control 1967-1968 Jun 9, 13 folders (Box 54)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control 1968 Jun 10-Jul 8, 23 folders (Box 55)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control 1968 Jul 8-15, 27 folders (Box 56)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control 1968 Jul 15-Dec, 26 folders (Box 57)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control 1969-1972, 14 folders (Box 58)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Anti 1968 Jun 1-24, 6 folders (Box 58)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Anti 1968 Jun 25-Sep, 1971, 15 folders (Box 59)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Dodd Amendment 1968 (Box 59)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Jackson Amendment 1967 (Box 59)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Out of State 1968 (Box 59)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Petitions 1968 Jun-Jul 4, 5 folders (Box 59)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Petitions 1968 Jul 6-11, 5 folders (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Postcards 1968, 3 folders (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Gun Control - Tyding's Gun Registration Bill 1968 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Immigration and Naturalization 1967-1972 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Impeachment 1971 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Improvements in Judicial Machinery 1967-1972 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Internal Security 1967-1971 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Inventors (H.R. 1483) 1972 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Judgeships 1968-1972 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Judicial Districts in Virginia 1968 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Juvenile Delinquency 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - National Labor Relations Board 1970 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Nominations - Butzner 1967 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Nominations - Kleindienst 1972 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Nominations - Maletz 1967 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Nominations - Otepka 1969 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Nominations - Virginia 1967 (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Poor Peoples' March 1968, 4 folders (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Pornography 1968-1970, 4 folders (Box 60)
  - Judiciary - Pornography 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Judiciary - Prayer Amendment 1966-1972, 18 folders (Box 61)
  - Judiciary - Prayer Amendment - Postcards 1968 Jun (Box 61)
  - Judiciary - Prayer in Space 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box 61)
  - Judiciary - Prison Reform 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Judiciary - Privacy Bill 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Judiciary - Privacy of Federal Employees 1966-1967 (Box 61)
  - Judiciary - Private Bill - Alexander, Robert 1967 & 1971, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Judiciary - Private Bill - Monier, Ltd. 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 62)
  - Judiciary -Private Bills A-Z 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Rules and Administration - Rule 22 1967 (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Safe Streets Bill 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Separation of Powers 1967-1972 (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Six Year Presidential Term 1971 (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Subversive Activities 1967 (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Blackmun 1970 (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Carswell 1970 Jan-Mar 9, 5 folders (Box 62)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Carswell 1970 Mar 10-Nov, 16 folders (Box 63)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Carswell- Representative Sample of Carswell Mail 1970 (Box 63)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Fortas 1968 Jun-Jul, 7 folders (Box 63)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Fortas 1968 Aug-1969, 15 folders (Box 64)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Fortas - Out of State Mail 1968 (Box 64)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Haynsworth 1970 (Box 64)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Haynsworth - Opposing 1969, 7 folders (Box 64)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Haynsworth - Supporting 1969 Jul-Nov 7, 5 folders (Box 64)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Haynsworth - Supporting 1969 Nov 8-Dec, 11 folders (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Marshall, Thurgood 1967, 3 folders (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Poff 1970-1971 (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Powell 1971-1972 (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - Supreme Court - Rehnquist 1971, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - Tax Exempt Status for Private Schools 1970 (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - TV Violence 1968 (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - Voting Rights Act 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - War Claims Act 1970 (Box 65)
  - Judiciary - Wiretaps 1967-1970 (Box 65)
  - Labor and Public Welfare 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 66)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Appropriations 1968-1972, 9 folders (Box 66)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 66)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Advance Funding Commission 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Busing 1970, 1971 Jan-Jul, 3 folders (Box 66)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Busing 1971 Aug-1972 Mar 24, 24 folders (Box 67)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Busing 1972 Mar 27-Nov, 12 folders (Box 68)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Busing National Write Your Congressman Club Opinion Ballots 1972 Apr-May, 5 folders (Box 68)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Community College Act 1969 (Box 68)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Elementary & Secondary Education 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 68)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Elementary & Secondary Education - Surveys 1968, 11 folders (Box 69)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Emergency School Aid 1971 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Freedom of Choice 1969 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Freedom of Choice - Norfolk & Portsmouth 1969 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Head Start Program 1968-1970 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Higher Education, S. 659, etc. 1968-1972, 5 folders (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Higher Education - Student Loans 1971 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Higher Education - Student Unrest 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Impact Areas 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Job Corps 1969 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Learning Disabilities 1969-1970 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Library Funds 1969-1972 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Medical Student Aid 1969 (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - National Defense Education Act 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - National Endowment for the Arts 1968 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Sex Education 1970 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Survey of State Superintendents. SEE ALSO: Education - Elementary & Secondary Education Act - Surveys 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Tax Credits 1972, 4 folders (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Education - Vocational 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Employment & Manpower 1967-1972 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Employment & Manpower - Economic Opportunity Act (S. 1545) 1967 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Employment & Manpower - Emergency Employment Act (S. 3063) 1967-1968 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Employment & Manpower - Equal Employment Opportunities Enforcement Act 1967-1968 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Employment & Manpower - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (S. 1308) 1967 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Employment & Manpower - Office of Economic Opportunity 1967-1970 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health 1966-1972, 8 folders (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Appropriations 1970 (Box 71)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Black Lung Benefits 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 72)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Cancer Control Act, S. 34 1971-1972, 5 folders (Box 72)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - DES (diethylstilbestrol) in Beef Cattle S. 2818 1971-1972 (Box 72)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Family Planning / Population Control 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 72)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Family Planning / Population Control - Abortion 1970-1972, 4 folders (Box 72)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Food Supplement Amendment(S. 2517) 1969-1970 (Box 72)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Hill-Burton 1968-1970 (Box 72)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Hunger and Hunger Tour Files 1968-1971, 14 folders (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Lead Paint Poisoning 1972 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Medical Research 1970 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Mental Health 1968-1972 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Multiple Sclerosis Act 1972 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Narcotics and Alcohol 1969-1972, 5 folders (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - National Family Health Week 1968 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Nurse Training 1971 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Nutrition and Human Needs - Senate Select Committee 1969-1970 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Physicians (S. 3418) 1970 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Public Health Service Act (H.R. 6418) 1967-1970 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Radiation Safety Acts 1970-1971 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Sickle Cell Anemia 1971-1972 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Health - Sudden Infant Death Syndrome 1972 (Box 73)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Juvenile Delinquency Prevention 1967-1968 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor 1966-1972, 6 folders (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Coal Mine Safety 1969, 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Davis-Bacon Act Suspension 1971 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Emergency Public Protection Act (S. 3526) 1970 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Emergency Strike Bill (S. 3232) 1972 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission 1967, 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Fair Labor Standards Act 1967 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Federal Employee Freedom of Choice Act (S. 3483) 1968 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Handicapped Workers & Vocational Rehabilitation 1968 & 1972 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Labor/Management Relations Act Amendment (S. 1369) 1970 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Longshoremen & Harbor Workers' Compensation Act (S. 2318 & H.R. 12006) 1972 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Migrant Workers 1967 & 1970 (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Minimum Wage 1969-1972 Jun, 5 folders (Box 74)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Minimum Wage 1972 Jul-Nov, 4 folders (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - National Federation of Independent Business Ballots 1967 (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - National Labor Relations Act Amendment re Agricultural Workers (S. 8) 1968 (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - National Labor Relations Act Amendment re Hospitals (H.R. 11357) 1972 (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Occupational Safety and Health Act, S. 2864 1968-1972, 7 folders (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Private Pension Plans 1971-1972 (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Railroad Retirement 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Right-to-Work 1967 & 1972 (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Situs Picketing 1967 & 1969, 2 folders (Box 75)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Strikes 1968-1972 (Box 76)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Strikes - Dock Workers 1971-1972 (Box 76)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Strikes - Railroad 1967-1971, 6 folders (Box 76)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Labor - Union Dues & Membership 1971-1972 (Box 76)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Poverty and Welfare Bills 1967-1972, 10 folders (Box 76)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Veterans' Affairs 1967-1970 (Box 76)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Veterans' Affairs - Hospitals 1970 (Box 76)
  - Labor and Public Welfare - Welfare Funds in Virginia 1966-1968 (Box 76)
  - Post Office and Civil Service 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Census 1967-1969 May, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Census 1969 Jun-1971 (Box 77)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Dual Compensation 1967-1972 (Box 77)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Federal Employee Pay Raise 1967, 3 folders (Box 77)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Federal Pay Freeze 1971, 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Hatch Act 1966-1972, 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Manpower 1967 & 1971 (Box 77)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Position Classification 1967 (Box 77)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Nominations - Virginia 1st District through 8th District 1967-1970, 13 folders (Box 77)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Nominations - Virginia 9th District through 10th District 1967-1969, 5 folders (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Rates and Pay Raises, H.R. 7977, H.R. 10,000. H.R. 13.000 1966-1972, 6 folders (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Reform 1969-1970, 4 folders (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Service 1966-1968 (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Service - News Releases 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Service - Personnel Actions 1970 (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Service - Postmasters' Examinations 1967-1968 (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Service - Rural Carriers' Examinations 1967-1968 (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Service - Third Class Mail Increase (Form Letter Reply) 1967 (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Postal Strike 1970 (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 78)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement 1969-1972, 7 folders (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement - Annuities 1971-1972, 5 folders (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement - Combination 80 1970-1972 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement - Cost of Living 1969-1972 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement - Federal-State Cooperative Programs 1968-1972 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement - Firefighters 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement - Health Benefits 1967-1972 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement - National Guard Technicians 1972 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Retirement - Social Security 1971-1972 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Salary 1970-1972 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Veterans 1972 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Voter Registration 1970-1971 (Box 79)
  - Post Office and Civil Service - Wage Board Determination Act 1970-1972, 5 folders (Box 79)
  - Public Works 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appalachia 1966-1969, 4 folders (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appalachia - Congress for Appalachian Development 1967 (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appalachia - Regional Development Act Amendments 1965-1972, 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appalachia - Summary of Proposals 1967 (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appropriations 1968-1972 (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appropriations - Civilian Atomic Reactors 1967 (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appropriations - Disaster Relief Subcommittee 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appropriations - Federal Sewage Treatment Grants 1969 (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appropriations - Hampton Roads 1969-1972 (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appropriations - James River Deepening 1969 (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Appropriations - Salem Church 1971, 3 folders (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Compacts 1967-1968 (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Disaster Relief 1970, 3 folders (Box 80)
  - Public Works - Disaster Relief 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Disaster Relief - Mississippi Hearings 1970 (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Disaster Relief - Roanoke Hearings 1970 (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Disaster Relief - Salvation Army 1970 (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Economic Development 1970-1972 (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Economic Development - Appalachia 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Economic Development - Kimballton 1971 (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Economic Development - Piney River 1970-1971 (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Economic Development - Saltville, Smyth County 1971-1972, 5 folders (Box 81)
  - Public Works - General Statements 1970-1971, n.d. (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Hunting Creek Landfill 1968-1971 (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Air 1967-1970 Sep, 11 folders (Box 81)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Air 1970 Oct-1972, 8 folders (Box 82)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Air - Air Quality Act S.780 1967, 2 folders (Box 82)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Air - Clean Air Amendments S. 3329, Muskie's Bill 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 82)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Air & Water 1966-1971, 9 folders (Box 82)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Air & Water 1972, 4 folders (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Environmental Advertising Bill S. 927 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Environmental Advertising Bill S. 927 - Dissertation by Peter M. Sandman 1971 (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Noise 1970-1972 (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Oil 1967-1971 (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Oil - Steuart Petroleum at Piney Point, Maryland 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Solid Waste 1969-1972 (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Statements ca. 1970-1972 (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Thermal 1966-1971, 2 folders (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Water 1966-1970 Feb, 6 folders (Box 83)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Water 1970 Mar-1972, 10 folders (Box 84)
  - Public Works- Pollution - Water - Federal Water Pollution Control Act S. 2525 re Vessel Pollution 1968, 2 folders (Box 84)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Water - Federal Water Pollution Control Act S. 2770 Amendment 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 84)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Water - Subcommittee on Air and Water Pollution Oversight Hearings 1967 (Box 84)
  - Public Works - Pollution - Water - Water Quality Improvement Act S. 7 & S. 3206 1967-1970, 5 folders (Box 84)
  - Public Works - Public Buildings and Grounds 1967-1971 (Box 84)
  - Public Works - Public Buildings and Grounds S. 1039 1967 (Box 84)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors 1969-1972, 4 folders (Box 85)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Beach Erosion 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 85)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Beach Erosion - Norfolk Study n.d. (Box 85)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Buena Vista Project 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 85)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Flood Control 1965-1967 (Box 85)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Hampton Roads Deepening 1969-1970 (Box 85)